question_data = [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Geography",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Ottawa is the capital of Canada.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Animals",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "A flock of crows is known as a homicide.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "The weapon Clint Eastwood uses in &quot;Dirty Harry&quot; was a .44 Automag.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "In the &quot;Kagerou Daze&quot; series, Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Franz Joseph I was the last emperor of Austria.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        }
    ]
